# Spencer Spezzano

San Francisco, CA smspezzano@gmail.com | 415-672-0555 http://www.linkedin.com/in/spencerspezzano https://github.com/smspezzano

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Front and back end web developer with a passion for creating clean and useful products that improve people's lives. I love working on all aspects of a website from analytics to user experience to building restful APIs. Quick learner who's not afraid to jump into a project where I don't know the language or framework - because I've done it before. Almost 3 years of working in a startup environment both on the development and business side.

#### **TECHNICAL TOOLBOX**

- Languages JavaScript, Ruby, Python, CoffeeScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Frameworks Ruby on Rails, Django, AngularJS, Backbone.js
- Misc: jQuery, PostgreSQL, RSpec, Protractor, Jasmine, Git, Heroku, BDD/TDD, AWS, lodash, Underscore.js, Mixpanel, A/B testing, Pair programing, MongoDB

## RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

KidAdmit | Full Stack Web Developer | San Francisco, CA | Jun 2014 - Present

- Stack: Python, Django, JavaScript, and AngularJS.
- Member of a 3 person team that maintains the website and develops new features.
- Successful history of independently completing projects tasked to me from start to finish under strict deadlines.
- Implemented a new marketplace structure to help direct future projects.
- Ability to quickly diagnose errors and implement long lasting solutions.
- Contribute to product growth meetings.

General Assembly | Web Developer In Training | San Francisco, CA | Jan 2014 - Mar 2014

- Three month web development bootcamp.
- Learned everything from computer science basics to deploying a Rails app on Heroku.
- Built 3 fully functional Ruby on Rails web applications.

Thrillcall | Site and Partner Administrator | San Francisco, CA | Jan 2012 - Dec 2013

 Maintained current business relationships with ticket partners. Created new partnerships to augment Thrillcall's concert and artist data.

### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly, San Francisco

Web Development Immersive course Graduated March 2014

• University of California, Santa Cruz

Bachelor of Arts, History with concentration in Asia and Islamic World Dean's List Graduated June 2011